# STEFAN BOBROWSKI

## **WEB DEVELOPER**

https://stefanbobrowski.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/stefanbobrowski/

https://github.com/stefanbobrowski

https://stackoverflow.com/users/3317728/stefanbob

#### **SUMMARY**

Web Developer, Software Engineer, and Game Developer with over 10 years of experience. Passionate about creating exceptional applications that help people, writing clean & performant code, and learning the latest technology. Aspires to push the boundaries of user-experience and content creation.

#### **SKILLS**

JavaScript, React, React Testing Library, Redux Saga, GraphQL, AWS, Git, Github, Node, Express, MongoDB, SCSS, Vue, Unreal Engine 5, Premiere Pro, Photoshop

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Home Depot - Remote - Software Engineer

May 2021 - present

Primary Skills: React, React Testing Library, GraphQL, Apollo, Github, Git

**Vibrant Software** - *Remote* - Software Developer

July 2020 - January 2021

Primary Skills: React, Redux Saga, Express API, AWS

Hat Trick Designs LLC - New York, NY - Full Stack Web Developer

June 2019 - July 2020

Primary Skills: React Hooks, MERN

Direct Wines - Norwalk, CT - Front-End Web Developer

February 2019 - May 2019

Primary Skills: React, Vue, JavaScript, jQuery, Structured Data Markup, SEO

Kathy Kuo Home - New York, NY - Front-End Web Developer

January 2018 - September 2018

Primary Skills: UX/UI, ASP.NET MVC, Google Analytics

Archi FX LLC - Remote - Web Developer

August 2017 - January 2018

Primary Skills: JavaScript, SCSS, Flexbox, PHP

Healthcasts - New York, NY - Front-End Web Developer

December 2016 - July 2017

Primary Skills: CSS animations, Node.js/NPM

**Finalsite** - *Glastonbury, CT* - Front-End Web Developer

September 2014 - November 2016

Primary Skills: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Custom CMS

**oDesk** - *Remote* - Web Development Freelancer

November 2009 - July 2015

Primary Skills: HTML, CSS, SASS, JavaScript, Photoshop

### **EDUCATION**

**University of Connecticut** - Bachelor of Science in Computer Science 2010 -2014